Guide to the Richard Hell Papers 1944-2003 (Bulk 1969-2003) MSS.140
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series V: Photography
  - Subseries.A: Professional
    - B&W, 5" x 4" piece of Theresa Stern composite, version 12, yellowed, undated (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeve A29, Photo 52)
    - B&W, 5" x 9" piece of Theresa Stern composite, version 12, undated (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeve A30, Photo 53)
    - B&W, negative of Theresa Stern composite, undated (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeve A30a, Photo 53a)
    - Contact sheet of Theresa Stern composite photography, undated (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeve A31, Photo 54)
    - Negatives of Contact Sheet, Theresa Stern composite photos, undated (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeve A31Aa, Photo 54a)
    - B&W, 8"x10" of Theresa Stern composite, version 9, undated (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeve A32, Photo 54b)
    - Photocopy of Theresa Stern composite contact sheets, with writing on back: "Tom_36A, Hell_5A-6, and check 12A-13", undated (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeve A33, Photo 55)
    - Sleeve A34 Photo 56 B&W, 5x7"" of Tom Verlaine in striped" shirt and RH in spiky hair and black shirt and sunglasses, undated (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeve A35, Photo 57)
    - B&W, 5"x7", of Tom Verlaine and RH holding television, undated (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeve A36, Photo 58)
    - B&W, 5"x7", of Tom Verlaine and RH standing against brick wall, undated (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeve A37, Photo 59)
    - B&W, 5"x7", of Tom Verlaine and RH standing against brick wall, undated (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeve A38, Photo 60)
    - B&W, 8" x 10", of Tom Verlaine in white shirt, black pants standing, undated (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeve A39, Photo 61)
    - B&W, 8" x 10" of band, Television, RH holding tv, undated (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeve A40, Photo 62)
    - B&W, contact sheet of Television band photos, undated (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeve A40a, Photo 62a)
    - Negatives of Television band photos, undated (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeve A41, Photo 63)
    - Contact Sheet of Television band photos, contact photos have been cut out, undated (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeve A41a, Photo 63a)
    - Negatives for Contact sheet of Television band photos, undated (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeve A42, Photo 64)
    - Contact Sheet of band practice photos, undated (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeve A43, Photo 65)
    - Contact Sheet of band practice photos, undated (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeve A43a, Photo 64a, 65a)
    - Negatives of band practice photos, undated (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeve A43b, Photo 64b, 65b)
    - Negatives of band practice photos, undated (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeve A44, Photo 65)
    - Contact Sheet of Band Practice, undated (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeve A45, Photo 66)
    - Contact Sheet of RH singing, undated (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeve A46, Photo 67)
    - Contact Sheet of RH singing, undated (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeve A47, Photo 68)
    - Contact Sheet of RH singing, undated (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeve A48, Photo 69)
    - B & W, 5”x7”, RH in striped shirt and sunglasses with others, On back: Roberta Bayley stamp crossed out and Chris Stein written in, undated (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeve A49, Photo 70)
    - B & W, 5"x7", RH in striped shirt and sunglasses with others, On back: Roberta Bayley stamp crossed out and Chris Stein written in, undated (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeve A50, Photo 71)
    - B & W, 8”x10”, RH, Tom Verlaine and Television in concert, photographer: Bob Gruen, 1974 (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeve A51, Photo 72)
    - B & W, 8"x10", RH, Tom Verlaine and Television in concert, RH jumping in air with guitar, photographer: Suzan Carson, Sir Reel Productions, undated (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeve A52, Photo 73)
    - B & W, 8"x10", RH against white wall wearing white ripped shirt, photographer: Kate Simon, undated (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeve A53, Photo 74)
    - Contact Sheet of RH promo headshots, including “Voidoid" stickers on forehead, photographer: Kate Simon, undated (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeve A54, Photo 75)
    - Contact Sheet of RH promo ¾ body shots, white shirt and white background, photographer: Kate Simon, undated (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeve A55, Photo 76)
    - Contact Sheet of RH promo headshots, includes sunglasses and VOIDOID sticker on forehead, photographer: Kate Simon, undated (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeve A56, Photo 77)
    - Contact Sheet of RH promo full and ¾ body shots, white shirt, black pants and white background, photographer: Kate Simon, undated (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeve A57, Photo 78)
    - Contact Sheet of RH promo headshots, includes smoking photos, photographer: Kate Simon, undated (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeve A58, Photo 79)
    - B & W, 8"x10", RH singing, photographer: Kate Simon, undated (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeve A59, Photo 80)
    - B & W, 8"x10",unidentified person laying on sink, holding bottle and spitting, photographer: Kate Simon, undated (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeve A60, Photo 81)
    - B & W, 8"x10", Three unidentified with black shirts, photographer: Kate Simon, undated (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeve A61, Photo 82)
    - B & W, 8"x10", of miners, photographer: Kate Simon, undated (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeve A62, Photo 83)
    - B & W, 8"x10", close-up of line of miners, photographer: Kate Simon, undated (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeve A63, Photo 84)
    - B & W, 8"x10", unidentified woman in ripped t-shirt and spiked blond hair, photographer: Kate Simon, undated (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeve A64, Photo 85)
    - B & W, 8"x10", 2 unidentified men, wearing suit coats, one with blond hair and striped shirt, one with black hair and gold tooth, photographer: Kate Simon, undated (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeve A65, Photo 86)
    - B & W, 8"x10",two unidentified men, one with leather body stitched suit and hood, photographer: Kate Simon, undated (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeve A66, Photo 87)
    - B&W, 1"x1.5", RH and company playing pool, cut out from contact sheet, photographer: Kate Simon, undated (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeve A67, Photo 88)
    - B&W, 1"x1.5", RH and company standing outside CBGB’s, on back: 2, undated (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeve A68, Photo 89)
    - B&W, 1"x1.5", RH and company in front of CBGB’s, close-up, on back:3, undated (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeve A69, Photo 90)
    - B&W, polaroid, unidentified woman in leather coat, rocks and ocean in background, “Delson Rock", undated (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeve A70, Photo 91)
    - Color, Polaroid, unidentified posed in chalk outline in blood splattered white sheets, version1, undated (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeve A71, Photo 92)
    - Color, Polaroid, unidentified posed in chalk outline in blood splattered white sheets, version2, undated (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeve A72, Photo 93)
    - Color, Polaroid, RH and Tom Verlaine in concert, undated (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeve A72, Photo 94)
    - Color, Polaroid, RH and unidentified woman in black, version1, undated (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeve A73, Photo 95)
    - Color, Polaroid, unidentified woman in red pants with handkerchief over hair, written on bottom:“Gold records for you- champagne?", annotated on back: “For me!, undated (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeve 74, Photo 96)
    - Color, Polaroid, RH and unidentified woman in black, version 2, undated (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeve A75, Photo 97)
    - Color, Polaroid, RH and unidentified woman in black, version3, undated (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeve A76, Photo 98)
    - Color, Polaroid, Three unidentified with bouquet of flowers undated (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeve A77, Photo 99)
    - B&W, 5"x7", RH with gun, posed crouched behind a car, undated (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeve A78, Photo 100)
    - Negatives, B&W RH and band photos, undated (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeve A78a, Photo 100a)
    - Negatives, B&W RH and band photos, undated (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeve A78b, Photo 100b)
    - Negatives, qty.2, 2"x2", [RH] against wall in suit jacket, undated (Box Binder A, Folder Sleeve A78c, Photo 100c)
    - B&W, 8"x10", Richard Hell posed with gun outside white door, Photographer: Roberta Bayley, undated (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeve B1, Photo 1)
    - B&W, 8"x10",RH posed with gun crouched in pool of light in dark room, Photographer: Robert Bayley, undated (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeve B2, Photo 2)
    - B&W, 8"x10", The Heartbreakers with two band members cut out, undated (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeve B3, Photo 3)
    - B&W, 8"x10", RH and the Heartbreakers, Photographer: Roberta Bayley, undated (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeve B4, Photo 4)
    - B&W, 8"x10", RH and the Heartbreakers on fire escape. Photographer: Bob Gruen, (1997 annotated on back), date:[1975], undated (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeve B5, Photo 5)
    - B&W, 8"x10", RH and Heartbreakers on fire escape with guitar, Photographer: Bob Gruen, undated (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeve B6, Photo 6)
    - B&W, 8"x10", RH and others unidentified, one image cut out, Photographer: Chris Stein, undated (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeve B7, Photo 7)
    - B&W, 5"x7" RH and unidentified in concert, vertical, undated (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeve B8, Photo 8)
    - B&W, 5"x7",RH and unidentified in concert, vertical, undated (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeve B8, Photo 9)
    - B&W, 5"x7",RH and unidentified band in concert, RH singing, undated (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeve B9, Photo 10)
    - B&W, 8"x10", Richard Hell and The Voidoids promotional photo. Sire Records, undated (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeve B10, Photo 11)
    - B&W, 8"x10", RH and Voidoids, RH wearing shirt with triangles, negative marks on bottom of photo read “5 and 5A", undated (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeve B11, Photo 12)
    - B&W, 8"x10", RH and Voidoids, RH wearing shirt with triangles, one person has been cut out of image, Photographer: Roberta Bayley, undated (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeve B12, Photo 13)
    - B&W, 8"x10",, The Voidoids, with RH cut out, Photographer: Roberta Bayley, undated (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeve B13, Photo 14)
    - B&W, 8"x10", RH and unidentified Photographer: Roberta Bayley, undated (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeve B14, Photo 15)
    - B&W, 8"x10", RH and The Voidoids, RH smoking, negative marks on bottom read “4…4A", Photographer: Roberta Bayley, undated (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeve B15, Photo 16)
    - B&W, 8"x10", RH and The Voidoids, RH in sunglasses and The Voidoids t-shirt, Photographer: Roberta Bayley, undated (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeve B16, Photo 17)
    - B&W, 8"x10", RH and The Voidoids, close- up, RH with out sunglasses and in The Voidoids t-shirt, Photographer: Roberta Bayley (2 copies), undated (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeve B17, Photo 18)
    - B&W, 8"x10", RH and The Voidoids, RH in Voidoids t-shirt, with right shoulder towards camera, Photographer: Roberta Bayley, undated (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeve B18, Photo 19)
    - B&W, 5" x7", RH and The Voidoids, undated (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeve B19, Photo 20)
    - B&W, 8"x10", RH and The Voidoids in white room, RH wearing black suit, Photographer: Roberta Bayley, undated (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeve B20, Photo 21)
    - B&W, 8"x10", RH and The Voidoids, side view, RH in black suit, band member with sunglasses in back, Photographer: Roberta Bayley, undated (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeve B21, Photo 22)
    - B&W, 8"x10", RH and The Voidoids, RH in shirt with triangles, undated (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeve B22, Photo 23)
    - B&W, 5"x7" RH and The Voidoids, undated (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeve B23, Photo 24)
    - B&W, 8"x10",RH and The Voidoids in studio rehearsing, Photographer: Roberta Bayley, undated (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeve B24, Photo 25)
    - B&W, 4"x5", RH with microphone and head back, Photographer: Jon Wallen, undated (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeve B25, Photo 26)
    - B&W, 2"x4", photo of writing on t-shirt “The Voidoids", undated (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeve B25, Photo 27)
    - B&W, 3" x 4", overexposed RH in sunglasses, undated (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeve B25, Photo 28)
    - B&W, 3" x 4", RH in guitar store, photo taken through window glass, undated (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeve B25, Photo 29)
    - B&W, 3.5"x5", unidentified woman standing outside, with grass and trees in background, annotated on back, undated (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeve B26, Photo 30)
    - B&W, 4"x5", close-up of RH’s face and comic book, top has been cut to a half circle, undated (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeve B26, Photo 31)
    - B&W, 3.5"x4.5", unidentified woman, undated (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeve B27, Photo 32)
    - Negative of RH on couch, undated (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeve B27a, Photo 32a)
    - Negative of RH on guitar, undated (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeve B27a, Photo 33a)
    - Negative of RH with jacket, undated (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeve B27a, Photo 33a)
    - Negative of RH and The Voidoids, undated (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeve B27a, Photo 33a)
    - B&W, 8"x10", RH and unidentified woman Photographer: Roberta Bayley, undated (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeve B28, Photo 34)
    - B&W, 8"x10",RH promo shot, Photographer: Roberta Bayley, undated (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeve B29, Photo 35)
    - B&W, 8"x10", RH promo shot, Photographer: Roberta Bayley, undated (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeve B30, Photo 36)
    - B&W, 8"x10", closeup of RH face, Photographer: Roberta Bayley, undated (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeve B31, Photo 37)
    - B&W, 8"x10",, RH and unidentified man Photographer: Roberta Bayley, undated (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeve B32, Photo 38)
    - B&W, 5"x7", RH in trench coat and tie, undated (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeve B33, Photo 39)
    - B&W, 5"x7", RH and unidentified man, Photographer: Roberta Bayley, undated (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeve B33, Photo 40)
    - B&W, 8"x10", annotated on back: “Richard Hell on the set of “blank generation" with director [Lommel] and actress Carol Bouquet, Photographer: Roberta Bayley, undated (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeve B34, Photo 41)
    - B&W, 8"x10", RH and The Voidoids Photographer: Chris Stein, undated (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeve B35, Photo 42)
    - B&W, 8"x10", RH and The Voidoids, Photographer: Chris Stein, undated (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeve B36, Photo 43)
    - B&W, 8"x10", RH and unidentified man with eye patch, Photographer: Chris Stein, undated (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeve B37, Photo 44)
    - B&W, 8"x10", RH air boxing camera, undated (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeve B38, Photo 45)
    - B&W, 8"x10", RH and unidentified woman, Photographer: Roberta Bayley, undated (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeve B39, Photo 46)
    - B&W, 8"x10",, RH and unidentified man, Photographer: Bob Gruen, undated (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeve B40, Photo 47)
    - B&W, 5.5" x 9.5, The Ramones, undated (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeve B41, Photo 48)
    - B&W, 8"x10", RH and Deedee Ramone, Photographer: Roberta Bayley, undated (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeve B42, Photo 49)
    - B&W, 4"x7", photo of unidentified band, undated (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeve B43, Photo 50)
    - B&W, 5"x7", [movie still], outside Walt Disney building, Woman in car, sign reads “Sexy", on back no. 28, undated (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeve B43, Photo 51)
    - B&W, 8"x10", RH lighting unidentified man’s cigarette, undated (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeve B44, Photo 52)
    - B&W, 8"x10", RH at Max’s, Photographer: Dan Asher, Apr 1976 (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeve B45, Photo 53)
    - B&W, 8"x10",RH at Max’s, Photographer: Dan Asher, Apr 1976 (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeve B46, Photo 54)
    - B&W, 8"x10", RH and Iggy Pop, annotated on back: “Iggy Pop and RH, CBGB 1976", Photographer: Roberta Bayley, 1976 (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeve B47, Photo 55)
    - Sepia, 2.5"x7", RH and unidentified woman, annotated on back: NOID, Photographer: [C. George], undated (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeve B48, Photo 56)
    - B&W, 8"x10", RH and the The Voidoids, Photographer: Jimmy DeSana, undated (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeve B49, Photo 57)
    - B&W, 8"x10", close-up of RH face, Photographer: Jimmy De Sana, undated (Box Binder B, Folder Sleeve B50, Photo 58)
    - B&W, 8"x10", RH and The Voidoids in concert, Photographer: Dan Asher, undated (Box Binder C, Folder Sleeve C1, Photo 1)
    - B&W, 8"x10", RH and The Voidoids in concert, close-up of RH, Photographer: Dan Asher, undated (Box Binder C, Folder Sleeve C2, Photo 2)
    - B&W, 8"x10", RH and The Voidoids in concert, Photographer: Dan Asher, undated (Box Binder C, Folder Sleeve C3, Photo 3)
    - Photo 4 B&W, 8"x10",RH in studio, overexposed, undated (Box Binder C, Folder Sleeve C4, Photo 4)
    - B&W, 8"x10", RH and The Voidoids, in concert, undated (Box Binder C, Folder Sleeve C5, Photo 5)
    - B&W, 4"x 5", Negative of Blank Generation promotion, undated (Box Binder C, Folder Sleeve C6, Photo 6)
    - B&W, 2.5"x 4.5",Woman with sword, [RH] in striped shirt, group scene, undated (Box Binder C, Folder Sleeve C6, Photo 7)
    - B&W, 3.5"x5", RH in concert, undated (Box Binder C, Folder Sleeve C6, Photo 8)
    - B&W, 3.5"x5", RH and unidentified, undated (Box Binder C, Folder Sleeve C6, Photo 9)
    - B&W, 5"x7", RH in concert playing bass, wearing tank top, Photographer: Patty Heffley, undated (Box Binder C, Folder Sleeve C6, Photo 10)
    - B&W, 6"x8", RH promo shot for SIRE, undated (Box Binder C, Folder Sleeve C7, Photo 11)
    - B&W, 8"x10", RH promo shot for Singer management, SIRE, undated (Box Binder C, Folder Sleeve C8, Photo 12)
    - B&W, 6"x8", RH promo shot for Singer management, SIRE, undated (Box Binder C, Folder Sleeve C9, Photo 13)
    - B&W, 6"x8", RH promo shot for Singer management, SIRE, undated (Box Binder C, Folder Sleeve C10, Photo 14)
    - B&W, 8"x10", RH outside brick building, undated (Box Binder C, Folder Sleeve C11, Photo 15)
    - B&W, 8"x10", RH and The Voidoids standing outside brick building, undated (Box Binder C, Folder Sleeve C12, Photo 16)
    - B&W, 8"x10", RH and the Voidoids standing outside brick building, undated (Box Binder C, Folder Sleeve C13, Photo 17)
    - B&W, 8"x10", RH and The Voidoids, Photographer: Roberta Bayley, undated (Box Binder C, Folder Sleeve C14, Photo 18)
    - B&W, 8"x10", RH and band standing against brick wall, annotated on back: SIS (bricks), most recent, The Voidoids (that recorded Destiny Street), Thanks to J. Holmstrom, Photographer: Roberta Bayley, undated (Box Binder C, Folder Sleeve C15, Photo 19)
    - B&W, 8"x10", RH, Photographer: Roberta Bayley, undated (Box Binder C, Folder Sleeve C16, Photo 20)
    - B&W, 8"x10",RH and The Voidoids sitting inside, Photographer: Roberta Bayley, undated (Box Binder C, Folder Sleeve C17, Photo 21)
    - Color, Slide, RH and the Voidoids, undated (Box Binder C, Folder Sleeve C18, Photo 22)
    - Color, Slide, RH promo shot, undated (Box Binder C, Folder Sleeve C18, Photo 23)
    - Color, Slide, RH promo shot, undated (Box Binder C, Folder Sleeve C18, Photo 24)
    - B&W, 8"x10", RH sitting on couch in apartment, (2 copies), undated (Box Binder C, Folder Sleeve C19, Photo 25)
    - B&W, 7"x10", horizontal, RH sitting on couch in apartment, undated (Box Binder C, Folder Sleeve C20, Photo 26)
    - B&W, 8"x10", horizontal, RH sitting on couch in apartment, undated (Box Binder C, Folder Sleeve C21, Photo 27)
    - B&W, 6"x10", horizontal, RH sitting on couch in apartment, Photographer: Janice K Johnson, undated (Box Binder C, Folder Sleeve C22, Photo 28)
    - B&W, 8"x10", RH promo shot, (2 copies), Photographer: Roberta Bayley, undated (Box Binder C, Folder Sleeve C23, Photo 29)
    - Negative of: B&W, 8"x10", Full body promotional photo of RH in suit and black shirt, Photographer: Roberta Bayley, undated (Box Binder C, Folder Sleeve C23a, Photo 29a)
    - Color, 5"x7", Full body promotional photo of RH in suit and black shirt, Photographer: Roberta Bayley, undated (Box Binder C, Folder Sleeve C24, Photo 30)
    - Color, slide, RH full body promotional photo, in suit and black t-shirt, (10), Photographer: Roberta Bayley, undated (Box Binder C, Folder Sleeve C25, Photo 31)
    - B&W, 1.5" x 8" print of negatives of RH with human skull in various poses, undated (Box Binder C, Folder Sleeve C26, Photo 32)
    - B&W, 8"x10", RH sitting in chair, (2), undated (Box Binder C, Folder Sleeve C27, Photo 33)
    - Negative of: B&W, 8"x10", RH sitting in chair, (2), undated (Box Binder C, Folder Sleeve C27a, Photo 33a)
    - B&W, 8"x10", RH sitting, undated (Box Binder C, Folder Sleeve C28, Photo 34)
    - B&W, 8"x10", RH sitting, undated (Box Binder C, Folder Sleeve C29, Photo 35)
    - B&W, 8"x10", RH man sitting at table, undated (Box Binder C, Folder Sleeve C30, Photo 36)
    - B&W, 8"x10", RH sitting at table, undated (Box Binder C, Folder Sleeve C31, Photo 37)
    - B&W, 8"x10", Close-up of RH sitting at table, undated (Box Binder C, Folder Sleeve C32, Photo 38)
    - B&W, 8"x10", horizontal, RH sitting, undated (Box Binder C, Folder Sleeve C33, Photo 39)
    - B&W, 8"x10", horizontal, RH sitting at table, undated (Box Binder C, Folder Sleeve C34, Photo 40)
    - B&W, 8"x10", RH sitting at table with white table cloth, cigarette in hand and face to camera, Photographer: Roberta Bayley, undated (Box Binder C, Folder Sleeve C35, Photo 41)
    - B&W, 8"x10", RH and unidentified band in concert, undated (Box Binder C, Folder Sleeve C36, Photo 42)
    - B&W, 8"x10", RH and unidentified band in concert, RH in striped shirt singing, Photographer: Stephanie Chernikowski, undated (Box Binder C, Folder Sleeve C37, Photo 43)
    - B&W, 8"x10", RH standing against wall in button up shirt, Photographer: Bob Gruen, 1999 (Box Binder C, Folder Sleeve C38, Photo 44)
    - B&W, 5"x7", Written on left hand side: “The Facts of Death Photography", Top photo is RH kneeling over notepad, Bottom photo is close-up of RH ‘s face, annotated on back “City of Angels", 1978 (Box Binder C, Folder Sleeve C39, Photo 45)
    - B&W, 8"x10",, RH sitting, Photographer: Talfahrt, undated (Box Binder C, Folder Sleeve C40, Photo 46)
    - B&W, 8"x10", 3 unidentified people sitting, undated (Box Binder C, Folder Sleeve C41, Photo 47)
    - B&W, 8"x10", Lisa Robinson, “Voidoid Reviews…annotated on back; poetry/prose in pencil by RH, photographer: Kate Simon, undated (Box Binder C, Folder Sleeve C42, Photo 48)
    - B&W, 8"x10",unidentified woman, [Patti Palladin] with “No- you make me!!" written on chest, annotated on back of photo, “Patti Palladin, Snatch", undated (Box Binder C, Folder Sleeve C43, Photo 49)
    - B&W, 5"x7", [Patti Palladin] in black dress and fishnets, sitting/laying down on ground, undated (Box Binder C, Folder Sleeve C44, Photo 50)
    - B&W, 5"x7", unidentified woman, undated (Box Binder C, Folder Sleeve C45, Photo 51)
    - B&W, 8"x10", unidentified woman, undated (Box Binder C, Folder Sleeve C46, Photo 52)
    - B&W, 8"x10", RH in concert, annotated on back: [Torma], undated (Box Binder C, Folder Sleeve C47, Photo 53)
    - B&W, 5"x7", RH, annotated on back: “@ Pr—the city benefit public theatre for St.Marks", Photographer: Vivian Selbo, 1987 (Box Binder C, Folder Sleeve D1, Photo 1)
    - Color, 5"x7", RH and unidentified, undated (Box Binder C, Sleeve D2, Folder Photo 2)
    - Color, 5"x7", RH and unidentified man, undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D2, Photo 3)
    - Color, 5"x7", vertical, RH and unidentified man in room, undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D2, Photo 4)
    - Color, 8"x10", RH and unidentified man, undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D3, Photo 5)
    - B&W, 8"x10", RH full body promo photo, Annotated: “Overground" and “Richard Hell 1991", (2), Photographer Stephanie Chernikowski, 1992, 1991-1992 (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D4, Photo 6)
    - B&W, 8"x10", RH close-up, Photographer: Stephanie Chernikowski, undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D5, Photo 8)
    - Negative of RH Face and ¾ Body promo shot, Photographer: Stephanie Chernikowski RH Face and ¾ Body, RH wearing striped shirt and coat, looking to left of camera, Photographer: Stephanie Chernikowski, undated (Box Binder D, Folder Sleeve D4 & D5a, Photo D6 & D7a)